crystald.com 2005-06-22

# EidosInteractive.com

|   
---  
|  |   
| 

[The new Tomb Raider: Legend website is live. Check it out now!!](http://www.tombraider.com/)

[Check out some of the action in the new 25 to Life trailer…guns are blazing!!!](http://www.eidosinteractive.com/downloads/search.html?gmid=151)

|   
|  |   
---  
|  |   
| 

Register your new Eidos game to win.  
click here

|   
|  |   
---  
|  |   
| 

Go here to talk about the games! 

|   
|  |   
|  |  |  | 

**

EIDOS INTERACTIVE.S ONLINE

** PRIVACY POLICY

Eidos Interactive of the United States ("Eidos Interactive") respects the privacy rights of our online visitors and is committed to protecting the personal information collected about you. To further this commitment, we have adopted this Online Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") to guide how we collect, store, and use the information you provide us online. 

If you are a parent or guardian and are interested in knowing more about Eidos Interactive.s policy regarding the collection of information from children under 13, please see our special  childrens section below.

This Privacy Statement and the certification seal located on this page confirm that Eidos Interactive is a valid licensee and participating member in the [ Entertainment Software Rating Board's Privacy Online Program: ESRB Privacy Online.](http://www.esrb.com/) To protect your privacy, we have voluntarily undertaken this privacy initiative and all of our websites have been reviewed and certified by ESRB Privacy Online to meet established online information collection and use practices. As part of this privacy program, we are subject to frequent audits of our sites and other enforcement and accountability mechanisms administered independently by ESRB Privacy Online. 

Because the website you are currently visiting displays the ESRB Privacy Online certification seal, you can expect to be notified of the following.

  * The scope of this Privacy Policy

  * Exactly what information Eidos Interactive may collect from you through its website(s) 

  * How Eidos Interactive will use the information it collects 

  * What are the consequences if you refuse to divulge your personal information

  * Whether Eidos Interactive uses cookies or other passive collection tools on its website(s)

  * Who collects the information that you disclose on an Eidos Interactive website

  * With whom, if anyone, does Eidos Interactive share your personal information

  * What choices you can make regarding how your personal information is used

  * How you can change or delete the information Eidos Interactive has collected about you

  * What is Eidos Interactive's policy regarding collecting information from children under 13

  * How Eidos Interactive ensures the security, quality, and integrity of your information 

  * How you can ask a question or file a complaint regarding this Privacy Policy

**What does this Privacy Policy apply to?**  
The website you are currently visiting is operated by Eidos Interactive from its offices in the State of California, United States of America, located at 651 Brannan Street, Suite 400, San Francisco, CA 94107. This Privacy Policy currently applies to the following website(s) operated by Eidos Interactive (collectively referred to as the "Eidos Websites" or "our Websites"):  

[www.eidosinteractive.com](http://www.eidosinteractive.com/) [  
www.timesplittersgame.com](http://www.timesplittersgame.com/) [  
www.puppiestotherescue.com](http://www.puppiestotherescue.com/) [  
www.panzerclawsgame.com](http://www.panzerclawsgame.com/) [  
www.tombraider.com](http://www.tombraider.com/) [  
www.feareffect.com](http://www.feareffect.com/) [  
www.legacyofkain.com](http://www.legacyofkain.com/) [  
www.praetoriansgame.com](http://www.praetoriansgame.com/)   
[www.maddashracing.com](http://www.maddashracing.com/) [  
www.waverally.com](http://www.waverally.com/) [  
www.playfresh.com](http://www.playfresh.com/) [  
www.swingerzgolfgame.com](http://www.swingerzgolfgame.com/) [  
www.legaia2.com](http://www.legaia2.com/) [  
www.bywgame.com](http://www.bywgame.com/)   
[www.whiplashgame.com](http://www.whiplashgame.com/)[  
www.italianjobgame.com](http://www.italianjobgame.com/)[  
www.springbreakgame.net](http://www.springbreakgame.net/)[  
www.thiefgame.com](http://www.thiefgame.com/)

In the future, if we wish to include additional websites under this Privacy Policy, we will take reasonable steps to list them above and ensure that they provide a link to this Privacy Policy.

Please note that this Privacy Policy applies only to information submitted and collected online through the Eidos Websites (as listed above), and does not apply to information that may be collected by Eidos Interactive offline. In addition, this Privacy Policy does not extend to websites maintained by our international affiliates (e.g., Eidos UK, Eidos France, etc.) or to other companies or organizations to which we link. Because we cannot guarantee that the privacy policies of such sites meet our high standards and the requirements of the ESRB Privacy Online Program, we encourage you to read the privacy policy of the website to which you link before you submit any personal information to that site.

_Please note that by using our Websites, you signify your assent to Eidos Interactive.s Online Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use our Websites. We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy. Please check back from time to time to ensure that you are aware of these changes. Your continued use of our Websites will signify your acceptance of these changes.  _

**What types of information does Eidos Interactive collect?  **  
In order to give you the best experience on our Websites, Eidos Interactive may collect information about you, but only if you voluntarily provide it to us. Typically, we may ask you to submit personal and/or demographic information in connection with any one of the following features or services. 

Website registration   
Game-specific registration   
Newsletter subscription  
Online store  
Message boards  
Technical support  
Contests, sweepstakes, and other promotions  
Polls, surveys, or questionnaires  
Other features such as e-cards and tell-a-friend

The types and amount of personal information collected for these activities will vary depending on the activity. The requested personal information may include: your name, home address, telephone number, e-mail address and (for those purchasing products online) credit card information including billing and shipping addresses. For some activities, we may ask you to create a username and password and to provide other non-personal information such as your age or date of birth, gender, game and platform preferences (including information about the games and hardware you own), hobbies and interests, and other information (also known as "demographic information"). If demographic information is collected for an activity that also requires personal information, we may combine the demographic information with your personal information. Combining data allows us to customize the notices we send you and the content we provide you according to your interests and preferences. For more on how we use your information, please read the section on use below.   
No matter what method we use to collect information and no matter how we use that information, we will only collect the information deemed reasonably necessary to fulfill your online requests and our legitimate business objectives.   

**How does Eidos Interactive use the information it collects?**  
Generally, information that we collect for a particular purpose is used for that purpose only. For example, if you sign up for our newsletter, the email address that you provide will only be used to send you notices about special promotions, new products, or other events of interest and to otherwise keep you updated about our company. Information collected from those who register on our Websites is used to provide registrants the benefits associated with such registration (e.g., free tech support or access to the latest game news and exclusive store promotions). And, of course, any credit card information is used solely to fulfill and process purchase orders. In some instances, however, you may also be given the option to have your information used for an activity or service different from the activity or service that you were meaning to request (e.g., to have your name entered into a contest when subscribing to our newsletter or vice versa). If you choose to participate in these additional activities/services, Eidos Interactive will use your information to provide them to you.  
We may use your email address to send you service-related announcements that tell you about updates to our Privacy Policy, new areas or features on our Websites, changes to our online service or technical support policies, and other related changes. 

_**A Special Note about our Community Features**_

Please note that whenever you give out personal information in public areas such as community forums or bulletin boards, that information can be collected and used by people you don't know. While we strive to protect those who wish to participate in these activities, we cannot guarantee the security of, and are not responsible for, any information posted in these areas.  
What happens if I refuse to provide my personal information to Eidos Interactive?  
If you choose not to submit personal information when requested, you may not be able to participate in certain activities on our Websites and may limit the services we can provide you. For example, if you refuse to share your email address, you will not be able to receive our newsletter or otherwise register on our Websites. To simply browse our Websites, however, you do not need to give us any personal information.

**Does Eidos use cookies, track IP addresses, or use other passive means to collect information?  **

**_Cookies_**

We may use cookies to improve the use and functionality of our Websites. A "cookie" is a small file or record-keeping device that websites often store on a user's computer. Storage of cookies on your system provides an easy and convenient method for us to personalize your experience on our Websites. For example, cookies will remember your username and password and the products in your shopping cart, tell us that you have visited one of our Websites before, and may contain other information that will make your next visit to our Websites more enjoyable. We do not use cookies to collect personal information such as your name or to link your browsing habits to personal information already collected about you. You can always disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent to your computer.   
**  
_IP Addresses_**  
Eidos Interactive may keep track of Internet Protocol (IP) addresses to maintain website security and safety and to troubleshoot technical problems. An IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer every time you log on to the Internet.  
**  
_Log Files_**  
Eidos Interactive may collect information in the form of logs - files that record website activity and gather statistics about web users' browsing habits. These entries are generated anonymously, and help Eidos Interactive determine (among other things) how many and how often users have visited our Websites, which pages they've visited, and other similar data (a.k.a., navigational data). We also use the log file entries for our internal marketing and demographic studies, so we can constantly improve the online services we provide you. Log files are used internally only, and are not associated with any particular user, computer, or browser.  
**  
_Web Beacons_**  
We may use web beacons (or clear GIFs) on our Websites or include them in the e-mail messages we send you. Web beacons (also known as "web bugs") are small strings of code that provide a method of delivering a graphic image on a web page or in an email message for the purpose of transferring data. We use web beacons for many purposes, including site traffic reporting, unique visitor counts, advertising and email auditing and reporting, and personalization. We do not use web beacons to collect personal information such as your name or to link your browsing habits to personal information already collected about you.

**Who is collecting my personal information and is it shared with anyone?**  
The information that you disclose on the Eidos Websites is collected by Eidos Interactive or by a vendor on Eidos Interactive.s behalf; and, is used in accordance with the practices set forth above. Vendors (or agents) are entities that provide support for the internal operations of our Websites and who only use the information we share with them (or that they collect on our behalf) for purposes of internal fulfillment (e.g., online product fulfillment). Vendors are required to handle such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.  
We may disclose personal information in the good faith belief that we are required to do so by law, including but not limited to disclosure to law enforcement or other government officials in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose you or us to legal liability. In addition, in the event of a merger, acquisition, reorganization, bankruptcy, or other similar event, Eidos Interactive.s customer information may be transferred to our successor or assign, if permitted by and done in accordance with applicable law.

We do not sell, rent, or otherwise disclose your personal information to any other third parties.

**Can I choose how my personal information is used?  **  
If you do not want to receive our newsletter, service related announcements, or any other communications and/or services from Eidos Interactive, please opt-out from these communications or services at the time of registration or information collection. If you have opted-in and, at a later time, wish to opt-out, please contact us using the information provided below.  
In addition, along with many of the communications sent to you, Eidos Interactive provides you the opportunity to discontinue receiving future communications (i.e., unsubscribe).

**How can I access my personal information?  **  
If you wish to review, update, or delete any personal information that we may have collected about you, please contact us using the contact information provided below.

**What is Eidos Interactive's policy regarding children under 13?**  
Generally, Eidos Interactive does not knowingly collect personal information such as name and email address from children under 13 years old (.children.) on the Eidos Websites. However, from time to time, certain registrations on our Websites will allow children to sign up and disclose personal information, provided that Eidos has obtained prior and verifiable consent from the child.s parent or legal guardian (.parent.). To determine who is younger than 13 years old and whether parental consent is required for such registrations, we ask all users who wish to register to submit their date of birth. If a user indicates they are under 13 and the registration involved is available to children under 13, the child is then taken through our parental consent process. 

If given verifiable permission from a parent, Eidos Interactive will collect and store some or all of the following types of personal information about the child and his/her parent: child.s name, child.s email address, child.s mailing address, parent's name, and parent.s email address. We may also collect the child.s date of birth and link it to the child's personal information. Eidos will only collect this information if it is voluntarily submitted to us by the child or parent and with the parent.s approval. We do not collect personal information about a child through the use of passive collection mechanisms such as cookies; however, we may link a child.s profile to a cookie so that a parent can come back to our site and view or modify their child.s profile. For more information on how we use cookies and other information collection tools, please see our section on  cookies above.

  Once collected, a child's registration information will be used to provide the child the benefits that come along with the particular registration. These benefits typically include a free newsletter, free game play, and (in some instances) a free giveaway. We may also use children.s information for our internal marketing and demographic studies, so we can constantly improve and customize the products and services we provide to our website visitors.

  Please note that we are prohibited from conditioning a child's participation in an activity - like registration - on the child's disclosure of more personal information than is reasonably necessary to participate in the activity. This means that if we don't need a specific piece of information (like the child's phone number) to allow the child to register, we simply won't ask for it. We also take steps to protect the confidentiality, security, and integrity of children's personal information. To learn more about these steps, please see our section on  security below.

From time to time, certain portions of the Eidos Websites may allow children under 13 to disclose a limited amount of personal information without first telling us their age or getting their parent.s permission. Such portions of our Websites operate activities or provide services in a way that does not require prior parental consent.

Contact Information   
Any personal information that a child discloses on our Websites is collected by Eidos Interactive or by a vendor on Eidos Interactive.s behalf. Eidos Interactive.s complete  contact information is available below.

Disclosure of Children's Personal Information  
Please read our section titled " Who is collecting my personal information and is it shared with anyone?"  (above) for our policy on the disclosure of personal information collected from children under 13.

Parental Access  
A parent who has given Eidos Interactive permission to collect and use their child's personal information for a specific registration can, at any time, do the following: (1) view, modify, or have deleted the child's personal information; (2) discontinue further use or online collection of the child's personal information; and/or, (3) revoke his/her earlier consent to collect and use the child.s personal information. To do so, please visit the appropriate online profile area (provided during the consent process) and we will be happy to honor your request. To revoke your consent, simply deactivate your child.s account using the online profile area. As an alternative, you may contact us using the contact information below. 

**What safeguards does Eidos Interactive use to protect my personal information? **  
Eidos Interactive maintains reasonable procedures to protect the confidentiality, security, and integrity of the personal information collected from our website visitors, including children under 13. Personal information collected by Eidos Interactive is stored behind a firewall. We also have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. For example, before we allow web users to access their personal information or their children's information, we verify their identity by requesting information such as their username and password.

**How do I ask a question or file a complaint? (Contact Information)**

If you have any questions, complaints, or comments regarding this Privacy Policy or our information collection practices, please contact our Privacy Policy Administrator at: 

Eidos Interactive  
Attn: Privacy Policy Administrator  
651 Brannan Street, Suite 400  
San Francisco, CA 94107  
(415) 547-1200

For complaints, you can also contact ESRB Privacy Online directly at [ www.esrb.org](http://www.esrb.com/) or by regular mail at 317 Madison Avenue, 22nd Floor, New York, NY 10017.  
This Privacy Policy was last updated on **December 23, 2004.**

 ****  
---|---|---|---
